

LIKNESHKANTH RAO

Software Engineer

PROFILE

Likneshkanth Rao, 22 years old. A responsible, precise and dedicated person. Self-motivated, willing to take up on various challenges and driven by self-confidence to achieve goals. My main objective now is to get a platform for my internship in a Software Engineering firm so that I will be able to grow, learn and utilize my skills and knowledge, fulfilling organizational goals as a dedicated employee.

CONTACT

PHONE:018-3111476

EMAIL:

likneshrao@gmail.com

REFEREE:

Nor Azizah Saadon, School of Computing,Faculty of Engineering, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia (UTM). 81310 UTM Johor Bahru,Malaysia.

Fax:+607 - 5565044

Email:azizahsaadon@utm.my

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science (Software Engineering)

September 2017 - Current

- Universiti Teknologi Malaysia, Skudai, Johor.
- CGPA as of semester 5 : 3.20

Foundation in Science (Pure Science)

June 2016 - June 2017

- Johor Matriculation College, Tangkak, Johor
- ➤ CGPA:3.86

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

> 3A 3A-3B+

WORK EXPERIENCE

Public Mutual HQ ,Bandar Sri Damansara,Kuala Lumpur (Temporary Staff)

January 2016-March 2016

Assisting senior staffs with their daily tasks.

Kikilala Aeon, Bukit Rajah, Klang, Selangor (Promoter)

June 2017 - August 2017

Promote products and assist customer.

Private Microsoft Office tutor

February 2020 - Current

Tutoring beginner,intermediate and advanced level of Microsoft Word, Excel and Powerpoint to a group of students

Coursework Project Experiences

Application Development (Car Rental Website)

> A website was developed using HTML, Javascript and PHP.

Software Development and Architecture (UTM Alumni System)

A system development using Enterprise Architect (EA) and Visual Studio with the use of C# and java language.

Web Programming (Lecturer – Students Appointment system)

A system developed using HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP

Object Oriented Programming (Online shopping cart system)

➤ A simple cart system developed using html, java and PHP Internet Programming (UTM sports hall booking system)

This system involves using servlet using glassfish server in the netbeans IDE.

ADDRESS:

2136,Jln RJ 2/25,Taman Rasah Jaya, 70300,Seremban,Negeri Sembilan.

SKILLS







Java:

C++:

PHP:

Javascript:

C# :

Leadership Skills

There are few important positions I have uphold:

- Vice Director of Project Helping Hands (2019) organized by Persatuan Mahasiswa Hindu (PMH).
- Programme Activity Executive for SUKAM organized by Kolej Tun Dr Ismail , UTM.
- Head of External Affairs Department for Ranggoli 4.0 (2019)